<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hina Sakazaki</title>
    <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hina Sakazaki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 20:29:45 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hinasakazaki.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Week Vacation to Tokyo &amp; Seoul</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/tokyoseoul2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/tokyoseoul2018/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my first travel post!
I went on a two week trip with 2 of my buddies and my fiance, Chris to Tokyo and Seoul.
Our flight was through Korean Air - SFO -&amp;gt; INC -&amp;gt; NRT, then HND -&amp;gt; GMP, and finally, INC -&amp;gt; SFO.
Table of Contents Day 1: Arrive, Teppan Baby
Day 2: Pumpkin Muffin and Family
Day 3: Meiji Jinguu, Ramen, Shopping Yakitori
Day 4: Tsukiji, Ginza Coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website!</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>I got sick of my old handmade frontend design, Django backend, so I decided to use Hugo to make my static website. I used the hugo-geo template. It was super easy and quick, and so much prettier. I highly recommend it!
Some screenshots of my old website:
I did enjoy the thumbnails for my projects, so I can see if I can do that here, too, itch.io style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THE Marriage Proposal Game</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/everyday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/everyday/</guid>
      <description>I made a game called Every Day The Game for my now fiance.
Note that the rest of the post is a direct copy of what is on my github project README.
Play Download at Itch.io
Watch PlayThrough Video on YouTube
Concept May or June of 2014, we celebrated our first year anniversary at a paint-your-stuff place and I painted this.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of it as a game idea, but a cutesy little design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Trip to Visual Novel Land</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/mymagicalbestfriend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/mymagicalbestfriend/</guid>
      <description>In December, I worked on a game called My (Magical) Best Friend! which is a visual novel inspired by anime (especially Madoka). It turns out that a youtuber made a Let&amp;rsquo;s Play Video of it.
It&amp;rsquo;s really great to see your game be played by someone who you don&amp;rsquo;t know, who plays games for the sake of playing games (unlike other Ludum Dares where people play your games so they can get votes as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iOS Audio Collaboration App: Sway</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/sway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/sway/</guid>
      <description>A non game! Made during CodePath iOS for Engineers Bootcamp.
We won first place!
Promo video
Description An app for capturing, sharing, and collaborating on musical ideas.
Walkthrough Previous walkthroughs: Wireframes For more details, take a look at our repository README.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You are the monster: Labor Day</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/laborday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/laborday/</guid>
      <description>Ludum Dare 33&amp;rsquo;s theme was &amp;ldquo;You are the Monster&amp;rdquo;.
With a theme like “You are the Monster”, and Labor Day in mind (I’m already excited for my 3 day weekend) I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but to remember recent controversies with Amazon– shedding light also to the warehouse worker conditions.
I don’t want to be too literal or heavyhanded. My goal is to make a small, cute game that has some satirical quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiplayer Tattoo Parlor</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/slingingink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/slingingink/</guid>
      <description>Hello!
I am currently finishing up a game called Slinging Ink.
You can play online multiplayer on the link.
Currently, we don&amp;rsquo;t have a tutorial level, so I thought to explain it here.
Thus begins our &amp;ldquo;How to Play&amp;rdquo;:
1) The main screen has three buttons, &amp;ldquo;Find Match&amp;rdquo; for going into matchmaking system and finding an opponent to play with. You might have to wait a bit for the opponent to get ready, so only do this if you have time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Love and Money</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/valentinesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/valentinesday/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be a quick one. In our Art 178 class we made a &amp;ldquo;quick loop&amp;rdquo; game. My quick loop was the following: boyfriend says he wants something &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; player works, makes money, buys it for him &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; boyfriend is happy and gives love
Yes, super strange and reductionalist. Oh well!
Eventually I added more features to the game by adding win/lose conditions:
 Win love by money</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently a Senior Software Engineer at Zynga where I work on shared client SDKs, a package management system for distributing SDKs across games, and do lots of recruiting/extracurriculars on the side (Read: Recruiting more women &amp;amp; diversity, play trombone, do mentorship). In my spare time, I lift weights (145lb squat), bake, play trombone, take photos of succulents, play, and make games.
How I got started When I was 4, I had my first computer on which I played Kid Pix with my little sister.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>