<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hina Sakazaki</title>
    <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hina Sakazaki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 17:50:45 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New House, Too Many Persimmons</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/persimmons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 17:50:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/persimmons/</guid>
      <description>Late Summer of 2020, my spouse and I purchased a home (a whole heap of fun which I don&amp;rsquo;t want to think about). While the various fruit trees that it came with weren&amp;rsquo;t the deciding factor, it certainly seems that they will become a large part of our lifestyle.
We&amp;rsquo;ve only lived here for almost three months, and we&amp;rsquo;ve already spent quite a bit of effort on the hachiya persimmons for a good two months:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LD46 Love Is Alive: A Couples Therapist Keeps Love Alive</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/loveisalive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/loveisalive/</guid>
      <description>This is a game I submitted for LD46 game jam.
Play at: https://hinerz.itch.io/love-is-alive
GitHub: https://github.com/hinasakazaki/LD46
First, a .gif to start off things&amp;hellip; In the midst of shelter-in-home, I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching a reality show called Love is Blind like many other consumers. In addition to that, I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching &amp;ldquo;Couples Therapist Reacts to Love is Blind&amp;rdquo; on YouTube and it&amp;rsquo;s been surprisingly insightful! link here
Having been shut in with my spouse for over a month now, I am increasingly thankful for vulnerable moments, and aware of walls that we put up when we are unhappy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Journey to my Signature Soap Recipe</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/soapmaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/soapmaking/</guid>
      <description>I started soaping for the following reasons:
 We had old oil we used for frying that we failed to take to the recycling center during our move in 2017. We had a gallon of old canola oil that one of my old roommates left between 2014 and 2015. My spouse eats a lot of bacon due to his keto diet.  My mom had told me before that my grandma would make something called 廃油石鹸, which in English means &amp;ldquo;Waste oil soap&amp;rdquo; back in the day with old frying oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story-based Japanese Games 2014-2019 Reviews</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/somegamereviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 17:47:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/somegamereviews/</guid>
      <description>While I&amp;rsquo;m stuck at home for social distancing, I thought I might take time to casually review some of my games for my own recordkeeping. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to play Nier: Automata (which I&amp;rsquo;m kind of failing at) and it&amp;rsquo;s been making me think about other Japanese single player games I&amp;rsquo;ve played.
To limit the number of games I review in this post, I&amp;rsquo;ve artificially limited them to:
 Japanese Single-player Story based (so no Animal Crossing) I played &amp;gt;= 10 hours of and completed at least one round of (so no Bravely Default or Yakuza series, or short free games)  I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to capture my thoughts so that I don&amp;rsquo;t have to later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer 2019 Hair Expedition</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/hairexpedition2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 13:25:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/hairexpedition2019/</guid>
      <description>Like a typical femme-person-about-to-get-married, I grew my hair out for the wedding. The 20 inches of thick, healthy hair performed well on our big day, and by that time, I was so sick of having the same hair. Historically I had done all sorts of stuff (color, ombre, side-buzz…), and finally, I could unleash my creativity and apply the scientific method on this long, substantive canvas once again.
I used to get my hair bleached and colored at a salon in Berkeley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for the Second SWE Gig</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/jobswitch2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 16:02:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/jobswitch2018/</guid>
      <description>I had a great 2 years and 10 months of incredible learning and fun at Zynga, but in November 2017, I decided that it was a good time to look for a new opportunity.
I started my new job at Google in April 2018, and now that I&amp;rsquo;ve been at my new workplace for 6 months, I&amp;rsquo;d like to talk about my strategy and advice for switching jobs a few years out of college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Switch and Weekend Seattle Trip</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/seattle2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 12:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/seattle2018/</guid>
      <description>After two years and ten months, my last day at Zynga was April 13th.
Before starting my new job at Google I decided to take a super short weekend trip to Seattle to visit my younger sister who is doing her PhD at University of Washington.
It was super rainy, but still lots of fun. The highlights were H-Mart, the Link Light Rail transportation system, the Duke Ellington Orchestra at the Seattle Symphony, the Japanese Baptist Church, the Seattle Japanese Garden, and the UDub campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Week Vacation to Tokyo &amp; Seoul</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/tokyoseoul2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/tokyoseoul2018/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my first travel post!
I went on a two week trip with 2 of my buddies and my fiance, Chris to Tokyo and Seoul.
Our flight was through Korean Air - SFO -&amp;gt; ICN -&amp;gt; NRT, then HND -&amp;gt; GMP, and finally, ICN -&amp;gt; SFO.
Table of Contents Day 1: Arrive, Teppan Baby
Day 2: Pumpkin Muffin and Family
Day 3: Meiji Jinguu, Ramen, Shopping Yakitori
Day 4: Tsukiji, Ginza Coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website!</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>I got sick of my old handmade frontend design, Django backend, so I decided to use Hugo to make my static website. I used the hugo-geo template. It was super easy and quick, and so much prettier. I highly recommend it!
Some screenshots of my old website:
I did enjoy the thumbnails for my projects, so I can see if I can do that here, too, itch.io style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THE Marriage Proposal Game</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/everyday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/everyday/</guid>
      <description>I made a game called Every Day The Game for my now fiance.
Note that the rest of the post is a direct copy of what is on my github project README.
Play Download at Itch.io
Watch PlayThrough Video on YouTube
Concept May or June of 2014, we celebrated our first year anniversary at a paint-your-stuff place and I painted this.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of it as a game idea, but a cutesy little design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Trip to Visual Novel Land</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/mymagicalbestfriend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/mymagicalbestfriend/</guid>
      <description>In December, I worked on a game called My (Magical) Best Friend! which is a visual novel inspired by anime (especially Madoka). It turns out that a youtuber made a Let&amp;rsquo;s Play Video of it.
It&amp;rsquo;s really great to see your game be played by someone who you don&amp;rsquo;t know, who plays games for the sake of playing games (unlike other Ludum Dares where people play your games so they can get votes as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iOS Audio Collaboration App: Sway</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/sway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/sway/</guid>
      <description>A non game! Made during CodePath iOS for Engineers Bootcamp.
We won first place!
Promo video
Description An app for capturing, sharing, and collaborating on musical ideas.
Walkthrough Previous walkthroughs: Wireframes For more details, take a look at our repository README.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You are the monster: Labor Day</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/laborday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/laborday/</guid>
      <description>Ludum Dare 33&amp;rsquo;s theme was &amp;ldquo;You are the Monster&amp;rdquo;.
With a theme like “You are the Monster”, and Labor Day in mind (I’m already excited for my 3 day weekend) I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but to remember recent controversies with Amazon– shedding light also to the warehouse worker conditions.
I don’t want to be too literal or heavyhanded. My goal is to make a small, cute game that has some satirical quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiplayer Tattoo Parlor</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/slingingink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/slingingink/</guid>
      <description>Hello!
I am currently finishing up a game called Slinging Ink.
You can play online multiplayer on the link.
Currently, we don&amp;rsquo;t have a tutorial level, so I thought to explain it here.
Thus begins our &amp;ldquo;How to Play&amp;rdquo;:
1) The main screen has three buttons, &amp;ldquo;Find Match&amp;rdquo; for going into matchmaking system and finding an opponent to play with. You might have to wait a bit for the opponent to get ready, so only do this if you have time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Love and Money</title>
      <link>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/valentinesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 20:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hinasakazaki.github.io/post/valentinesday/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be a quick one. In our Art 178 class we made a &amp;ldquo;quick loop&amp;rdquo; game. My quick loop was the following: boyfriend says he wants something &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; player works, makes money, buys it for him &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; boyfriend is happy and gives love
Yes, super strange and reductionalist. Oh well!
Eventually I added more features to the game by adding win/lose conditions:
 Win love by money</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>